[Music]
what if every single person on this
planet is already doing the best job
they know how to do it'd be scary
because we look out we see chaos we see
destruction and if this is the best they
know how to do how do we improve by
honoring that everyone's doing the best
job they know how to do therefore if we
want them to do better collectively we
have to ask how how can we help you
without yelling at people without
demanding they do better our version of
better what do you need what tools can
we co-create to make it easier for you
to make it cheaper for you to give you
access to the information
and that is what we were going to create
together the platform to have those
conversations and the tools that make it
easier the tools if we want to eat
better the tools that help us eat better
looking at why we're not currently if we
want to manage our emotions better why
aren't we what tools are in place
there's never going to be a
one-size-fits-all but creating a system
that honors that it honors that we're
never going to get to perfect but we can
keep incrementally making it better and
better by asking how can we help and
creating the system that helps us get
together with other people who share the
same issues and co-create solutions
together I may not be able to fix my
diet by myself
I'm already doing the best I can with
what I've been given but together we can
bulk-buy it can bring down my costs
together we can put in the mental spoon
so that I don't have to think what's for
dinner every night together we can
create an entire company around food and
food delivery so that it's accessible to
all socioeconomic status not just the
rich to have your groceries deliver it
and have food prepped that we're meeting
ourselves where we are instead of
demanding we do better
what if everyone's already doing the
best job they know how to do then all we
can do is ask how can I help how can we
help and create those tools and that is
what we are doing to do please like and
subscribe and I'll see you tomorrow